AHMED AYMAN ABDELNABY

Backend Developer

Egypt, Cairo | +201090738568 | ahmed.ayman2516@gmail.com

SUMMARY:

I am a fresh graduate from the Faculty of Computers and Artificial Intelligence Benha University. I am a backend web developer with experience in PHP and Laravel. I have experience working with databases, and application programming interface (APIs). I passionate about learning new technologies and staying up to date with the latest trends in web development.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Ejad Tech

Odoo Developer Intern | 28 August 2023 - 4 October 2023

- Developed custom addons of Odoo ERP (Enterprising Resource Planning)
- Improved daily processes and task activities by designing and creating custom modules to meet specific business needs.
- Create websites using Odoo portal.

Orange Digital Center Egypt

Backend Web Developer Intern | 11 September 2022 - 15 October 2022

- Participating in coding training and events.
- Build and maintain websites using HTML5, CSS3, PHP, MySQL, and Laravel Framework.
- Creating and maintaining MySQL databases for storing and retrieving data
- Collaborate with other interns on various projects to update the website and create new features.

First Gulf Solutions

Automation Engineer Intern | 16 August 2022 - 05 September 2022

- Developing Automation tasks using Robotic process automation (RPA).
- Developing web applications using HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap and JavaScript.
- Created and tested applications for websites.

RELEVANT PROJECTS:

Lite Notes

Lite-Notes is a note-taking app that helps you capture and manage your thoughts and ideas and stores your notes securely on your device.

Technologies: Laravel, PHP, Tailwind CSS, and MySQL.

To-Do List

To-Do app is a simple app to write tasks you need to complete or things that you want to do. Technologies: Laravel, PHP, Bootstrap, and MySQL.

Authentication System

Authentication System is a simple system for three operations the login, logout and register. Technologies: PHP, Bootstrap, and MySQL

EDUCATION:

2019 - 2023 | Benha University

Bachelor of Computer Science

SKILLS:

- C++
- Object Oriented Programming
- Data Structures
- Algorithms
- Database
- Operating systems

- HTML
- CSS3
- Bootstrap
- Python
- PHP
- MySQL

- PostgreSQL
- Laravel
- Research
- Communication
- Git & GitHub
- Teamwork
- Self-Motivated
- Problem Solver